George and Ira Gershwin Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music (Box 1-63)
  - Song File (Box 53-55)
    - #49 Try
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/9)
      - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; [1, 2] p. ea., No lyric (Box-folder 54/9)
    - #50 Ask me again
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/10)
      - 2 copyist manuscript piano-vocal scores; [1, 3] p. ea., No lyric (Box-folder 54/10)
      - Manuscript vocal part in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/10)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [11] p., Lyric for "What does it mean?" on p. [8] (Box-folder 54/10)
    - #51 For you, for me, for evermore, See "For you, for me, for evermore" from The shocking Miss Pilgrim, Box-Folder 33/24-25
    - #52 For you, for me, for ever, See "For you, for me, for evermore" from The shocking Miss Pilgrim, Box-Folder 33/24-25
    - #53 Version A
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/11)
    - #54 Molly on the shore
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., Incomplete, no lyric; Notes on p. [2] (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., No apparent musical relation to piano-vocal score (Box-folder 54/12)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/12)
    - #55 Freud and Jung and Adler, See "Freud and Jung and Adler" from Pardon my English, Box-Folder 20/1-3
    - #56 Vague ballad
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/13)
    - #57 All the livelong day, See "All the livelong day (and the long, long night)" from Kiss me, stupid, Box-Folder 11/1-3
    - #58 Wasting time
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/14)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 54/14)
    - #59 Sutton Place
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of William Daly; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/15)
    - #60 Soprano tune
      - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/16)
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/17)
    - #61 Untitled
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 54/18)
    - #62 Rainbow and You’re still the only one
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/19)
    - #63A Warm tune
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [1, 2] p., Optional obbligato (Box-folder 54/20)
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/20)
    - #63B Untitled
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/21)
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/21)
    - #64 Ever
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/22)
    - #65 Narrative
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p. (Box-folder 54/23)
    - #66A Acid tune
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/24)
    - #66B One step
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/25)
    - #67 I was feeling low
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., In caption: marked “9” [by] G. G. (Box-folder 54/26)
    - #68 Ingratiating tune
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/27)
    - #69 Anthemy fragment
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/28)
    - #70 Untitled
      - A notation on the packing description indicates that this item was “Sir” or “Siren.” Presumably the manuscript was removed, according to Michael Feinstein. (Box-folder 54/29)
    - #71 Together at last, See "Together at last" from Pardon my English Box-Folder 22/15-18
    - #72 Meadow serenade, See "Meadow serenade" from Strike up the band Box-Folder 37/14
    - #73 Duet -- Lonely boy, See "Lonely boy" from Porgy and Bess, Box-Folder 29/6-7
    - #74 I must remember
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/30)
    - #75 Gertie Lawrence type
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/31)
    - #76 Follies
      - Manuscript piano score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/32)
    - #77 Untitled
      - A notation on the packing description indicates that this item was intended for East Is West, and that the manuscripts were filed with that material. (Box-folder 54/33)
    - #78 Rich fragment
      - Manuscript piano score fragment in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p. (Box-folder 54/34)
    - #79 For Lily Pons
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [4] p. (Box-folder 54/35)
    - #80 Sing! Carry on!, See "Sing! Carry on!" from Strike up the band Box-Folder 38/9-10
    - #81 Sextette
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 8 p., No lyric; IG holograph lyric credit (Box-folder 54/36)
      - Typescript lyric sheet, Caption title: We’re six little nieces of our Uncle Sam (Box-folder 54/36)
    - #82 When our ship comes sailing in, See "When our ship comes sailing in" from Oh, Kay! Box-Folder 18/28
    - #83 Hoping that someday you'd care, See "Hoping that someday you'd care" from Strike up the band Box-Folder 36/19
    - #84 Gushing, See "Gushing" from Tell me more Box-Folder 39/35-40/2
    - #85 Under the cinnamon tree, See "Under the cinnamon tree" from East is West, Box-Folder 5/7-8
    - #86 The bad, bad men, See "The bad, bad men" from Lady, be good! Box-Folder 11/15-16
    - #87 Adored one, See "Adored one" from Show girl Box-Folder 34/3-4
    - #88 Evening star, See "Evening star" from Lady, be good! Box-Folder 12/1-3
    - #89 Phoebe
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [3] p., Emendations in an unidentified hand; In caption: verse usable (Box-folder 54/37)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [5] p. (Box-folder 54/37)
    - #90 It’s wonderful how love can understand
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; In caption in the hand of IG: verse used (Box-folder 54/38)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score fragment; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/38)
    - #91 Will you remember me, See "Will you remember me" from Lady, be good! Box-Folder 13/13
    - #92 Opening, Act II, See "Oh, this is such a lovely war [ 1927 ]" from Strike up the band Box-Folder 37/20-21
    - #93 Look to the stars
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p. (Box-folder 54/39)
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 54/39)
    - #94 Fairyland wedding
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [5] p., No lyric (Box-folder 54/40)
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 54/40)
    - #95 If we had known
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Emendations in the hand of GG (Box-folder 55/1)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [2] p. (Box-folder 55/1)
    - #96 Bebe
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; In caption in the hand of IG: good verse, good can-can chorus (Box-folder 55/2)
    - #97 Barcelona
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 3 p. (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 6 p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/3)
    - #98 Beautiful bird
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Stephen O. Jones; 5 p. (Box-folder 55/4)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [3] p., Notes in the hand of GG on p. [4] (Box-folder 55/4)
    - #99, See "The hurdy-gurdy man" from Chopin show, Box-Folder 2/9 and "A corner of heaven with you," Box-Folder 56/2
    - #100 Put me to the test, See "Put me to the test" from Damsel in distress Box-Folder 3/15-17
    - #101 I’m afraid this can’t (won’t) last
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 1] p., Unfinished, no lyric (Box-folder 55/5)
      - IG holograph lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 55/5)
    - #102 You just keep on asking
      - Manuscript piano-vocal sketch in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 1] p. (Box-folder 55/6)
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 55/6)
    - #103 I want somebody
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [1] p., Refrain only, no lyric (Box-folder 55/7)
    - #104 Leave it to love, See "Leave it to love" from Lady, be good!, Box-Folder 12/17
    - #105 I’m a poached egg, See "I'm a poached egg" from Kiss me, stupid, Box-Folder 11/4-6 and OV-1/3
    - #106 Gold mine
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; 2 p., Verse only, no lyric (Box-folder 55/8)
    - #107 Gather-ye-rosebuds, See "Gather-ye-rosebuds" from Tip toes, Box-Folder 41/25
    - #108 Your eyes, your smile, See "Your eyes, your smile" from Funny face, Box-Folder 7/15
    - #109 Acrobats, See "Acrobats" from Funny face, Box-Folder 6/1-2
    - #110 You’re mighty lucky
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; 12 [i.e. 1, 11] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/9)
      - Photocopied (ozalid) lyric sheet (Box-folder 55/9)
    - #111 Untitled
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric; On cover: dated June 8, 1930 (Box-folder 55/10)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/10)
    - #112 I just met an angel
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/11)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/11)
    - #113 In moderate tempo
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/12)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p. (Box-folder 55/12)
    - #114, See "You can't unscramble scrambled eggs" from Girl crazy, Box-Folder 9/22
    - #115 Machinery going mad
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/13)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/13)
    - #116 Opening II
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/14)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/14)
    - #117 Hot
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/15)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/15)
    - #118 Opening I
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/16)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/16)
    - #119 Humpty and dumpty
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1, 2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/17)
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [1, 1] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/17)
      - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [2] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/17)
    - #120 Waltz
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [3] p., No lyric (Box-folder 55/18)
    - #121 Piano piece
      - Copyist manuscript piano score; [3] p. (Box-folder 55/19)
      - Copyist manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 55/19)
    - #122 Ballad
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; [1] p., Unfinished (Box-folder 55/20)
    - #123 Fatherland, mother of the band, See "Fatherland, mother of the band" from Pardon my English, Box-Folder 19/17-20
    - #124 Call me John
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; 2 p., 1st version (Box-folder 55/21)
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Kay Swift; 2 p., 2nd version (Box-folder 55/21)
      - Manuscript piano score fragments in the hand of Kay Swift; [3] p., Laid in: 2 holograph letters from Kay Swift to IG, 1966 June 30; [1] p. ea.; Laid in: Holograph letter from Kay Swift to IG, 1966 June 24; [1] p.; Laid in: Typescript letter from IG to Kay Swift, 1966 July 12; [1] p.; Laid in: Kay Swift holograph envelope (Box-folder 55/21)
    - #125 You started it, See "You started it" from Delishious, Box-Folder 4/22-23
    - #126 Something peculiar, See "Something peculiar" from Piccadilly to Broadway, Box-Folder 28/31
  - Miscellaneous Music (Box 56-57)
    The miscellaneous music in the Gershwin collection is organized alphabetically by title.
    - Beautiful
      - GG holograph manuscript leadsheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/1)
    - A corner of heaven with you, See also "The hurdy-gurdy man" from Chopin show, Box-Folder 2/9
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Lyric in pencil (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Photocopied (ozalid) piano-vocal score; [4] p., In caption in the hand of IG: Same as "The Hurdy Gurdy Man" but this is an earlier version (Box-folder 56/2)
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Dawn of a new day
      - Sheet music, IG holograph annotation (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Don’t you remember
      - Copyist and GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; 2 p., Incomplete, no lyric; Piano part and credit in hand of GG (Box-folder 56/4)
    - England
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; 10 p., No lyric (Box-folder 56/5)
    - The flapper
      - Copyist manuscript lead sheet; [3] p. (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Fugue
      - GG holograph manuscript short score; [2] p., Incomplete (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Good little tune
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score in the hand of Albert Sirmay; 7 p., No lyric (Box-folder 56/8)
      - Photocopied lyric sheets; [2] p., Laid in: Letter from Al Kohn to Edgar Carter, 1976 June 7 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - In the heart of a geisha
      - Photocopied sheet music, Laid in: Letter from Melvin Parks to IG, 1971 July 15; Laid in: Letter from IG to Melvin Parks, 1971 July 29 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - Insert
      - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/10)
    - An introduction
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Introduction hot-Astaire
      - GG holograph manuscript short score; [2] p., Incomplete; GG holograph manuscript sketch with lyric in the hand of IG on p. [3] (Box-folder 56/12)
    - Irish dance
      - Stephen O. Jones holograph manuscript full score; 3 p. (Box-folder 56/13)
    - Japanese
      - Photocopied Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 7 p. (Box-folder 56/14)
    - King of jazz
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., No lyric; IG holograph credit in caption (Box-folder 56/15)
    - Long long ago on the Nile
      - GG holograph manuscript piano score; 2 p., Laid in: GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/16)
    - Longing
      - GG holograph manuscript leadsheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/17)
    - March
      - GG holograph manuscript piano score; [3] p., Verse only; Key of B-flat major (Box-folder 56/18)
      - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p., Key of G major; In caption: Sept 16, [19]26 A. M. (Box-folder 56/19)
    - Mexican dance
      - Frank Saddler holograph manuscript full score; 24 p., Laid in: IG typescript notes (Box-folder 56/20)
    - Miscellaneous GG tunes
      - In the hand of Kay Swift; [24] p. (Box-folder 56/21)
    - Miscellaneous sketches
      - GG holograph manuscripts; [3] p., Includes "Shall we dance?" on p. [3] (Box-folder 56/22)
    - Mischa, Yascha, Toscha, Sascha
      - Copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Copyright information in the hand of IG on p. [1]; Inscribed by Fritz Kreisler on p. [4] with an added cadenza for p. [3] (Box-folder 56/23)
      - Sheet music, Limited ed. (New York: Random House, 1932 ) (Box-folder 56/23)
      - IG holograph/typescript lyric sheets; [10] p. (Box-folder 56/23)
    - No question in my heart
      - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., T.B. Harms demonstration copy; Music by Jerome Kern (Box-folder 56/24)
      - Lyric sheet (Box-folder 56/24)
    - Now that we are one
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 56/25)
    - O land of mine, America
      - Photocopied piano-vocal score; [2] p., Reproduced from Hearst Newspapers article (Box-folder 56/26)
    - Once there were two of us
      - Typescript lyric sheet, Music by Jerome Kern (Box-folder 56/27)
    - One step
      - Photocopied GG holograph manuscript leadsheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/28)
    - Pastoral
      - GG holograph manuscript piano sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/29)
    - Ragging the Traumerei
      - GG holograph manuscript piano-vocal score; [3] p., No lyric; Laid in: Envelope with IG holograph notes (Box-folder 56/30)
    - The revolution is booming
      - GG holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 56/31)
    - Singing in the rain
      - Manuscript piano-vocal score; 5 p. (Box-folder 56/32)
      - Typescript lyric sheets; [3] p. (Box-folder 56/32)
    - Spring song
      - Manuscript melody sketch for violin; [1] p., Found with Pardon my English Secaucus materials (Box-folder 56/33)
    - Till then
      - Typescript lyric sheet (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Unidentified cello sketch
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Unidentified melody sketches
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/3)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/4)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/5)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Unidentified piano sketches
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p., Found with "Pay some attention to me" materials (Box-folder 57/7)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/8)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/9)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p., In caption: August 4, 1923 (Box-folder 57/10)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p., In caption: October 27, [19]21 (Box-folder 57/11)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 57/12)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 57/13)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Unidentified piano-vocal sketch
      - GG holograph manuscript; [3] p. (Box-folder 57/15)
    - Unidentified short score sketches
      - GG holograph manuscript; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/16)
      - GG holograph manuscript fragment; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/17)
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 57/18)
    - Unidentified piece for banjo
      - GG holograph manuscript leadsheet; [1] p., Laid in: photocopied photograph of Bill Bowen and Fred Van Eps (Box-folder 57/19)
    - West Point walk
      - GG holograph manuscript lead sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 57/20)
    - What I care!
      - Typescript lyric sheet; 1 p. (Box-folder 57/21)
    - Women of America
      - Photocopied copyist manuscript piano-vocal score; [4] p., Laid in: Typescript letter from Irene Dayton to IG, 1962 November 19; Laid in: 3 typescript letters from Dave Gordon to IG, 1962 Oct 22, 1962 October 24, 1962 November 13; Laid in: Holograph letter from Theodore Grouya to IG, 1976 January 16; Laid in: Typescript letter from IG to Dave Gordon, 1962 November 14 (Box-folder 57/22)
  - Music Notebooks and Composition Exercises (Box 58-59)
    The music notebooks and composition exercises in the Gershwin collection are organized alphabetically by title.
    - 501 W. 110th St. N.Y.C., GG holograph manuscript sketches; [1, 4] p.; In caption: 1921 October 6; p. 1: [Unidentified study]; p. 3: Kitty’s kisses; p. 4: [Titles of songs used in Oh, Kay]; p. 5: Maybe (Box-folder 58/1)
    - Black notebook, GG holograph manuscript sketches; 11 p.; [Undated]; p. 1: I was doing all right; p. 2: Wake up, brother, and dance; [Unidentified]; p. 3: [Unidentified]; My honor was at stake [Titled: Hot Dogs]; p. 4: I used to – but I don’t anymore; It’s nice to know; p. 5: Waltz; Yes, yes, oui, oui; p. 6: Hold on; [Unidentified]; p. 7: Love is here to stay; Ask me again; p. 8: [Unidentified]; Simple as A.B.C.; p. 9: [Unidentified]; Unforgettable; I got rhythm [untitled]; p. 10: [Unidentified]; p. 11: [Unidentified] (Box-folder 58/2)
    - Composition exercises, 1923 January 29 and February 1, 2 GG holograph manuscripts; [2] p. ea.; Laid in: IG holograph notes; [1] p. (Box-folder 58/3)
    - Figured choral, GG holograph manuscript short score; [1, 2] p.; On cover: 1921 July 27 (Box-folder 58/4)
    - Geo. M. Gershwin. tunes [1916-1922], GG holograph manuscript sketches; [40] p.; Some sketches have lyrics in the hand of IG; p. 1-2: Melodies; p. 3-4: Beautiful bird; p. 5-6: Ain’t love grand; p. 7-8: Year after year [Titled: Moonlight]; p. 8: He’s gone; p. 9-10: Nobody but you [untitled]; p. 11: We’re here because; p. 12: If I only had somebody like you; p. 13: Isn’t it wonderful; p. 14: Who’s winning; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 15: Melody; p. 16: Helen of Troy; p. 17: Yankee doodle blues [Titled: American blues]; p. 18: Foxtrot; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 19: Tune; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 20: Tune; p. 21: When do we dance? [untitled]; p. 22: [Unidentified]; p. 23: Somebody loves me [Titled: Tune]; p. 24: How about a boy? [Titled: One step]; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 25: [Unidentified]; [Unidentified fragment]; A little bit; p. 26: My baby; [Unidentified fragment]; Waltz; Little jazz bird; p. 27: [Unidentified fragments]; Rag tune (A raggy rhythm); p. 28: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 29: Anything for you; p. 30: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 31: Molly on the shore; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 32: Naughty baby [untitled]; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 33: Walking home with Angeline [untitled]; p. 34-35: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 36: [Unidentified fragment]; Maybe [untitled]; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 37-38: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 39: Waltz hayseed; [Unidentified fragment]; Tune; p. 40: Theme; One step; [Unidentified fragment] (Box-folder 58/5)
    - Girl crazy [notebook], GG holograph manuscript sketches; [40] p.; GG holograph manuscript sketches; [48] p.; On cover: 1930 July; Laid in: IG holograph/typescript notes; [6] p.; p. 1-6: Bronco busters; p. 9-12: The gambler of the West; p. 13: Of thee; p. 14: Tune; [Unidentified]; p. 15: [Unidentified fragment]; Oh you kid / Who’s charming? / I want a little more of what I got last night; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 16: [Unidentified – Sweet Packard?]; p. 17: How beautiful [untitled]; p. 18: Finale mat; [Unidentified fragment]; Some girls can bake a pie; p. 19: [Unidentified fragment]; Because, because; Garcon, s’il vous plait; p. 20: There’s no stopping us now; p. 21: Posterity is just around the corner; Finale mat; p. 22: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 23: Love is sweeping the country [untitled]; p. 24-25: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 26: The dimple on my knee; Because, because [untitled]; p. 27: Because, because; p. 28: Jilted; Love walked in [untitled]; p. 29: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 30: Entrance of Supreme Court judges; p. 31: Trumpeter blow your golden horn [Titled: Bless our president]; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 32: A kiss for Cinderella [untitled]; p. 33: Who is the lucky girl to be? [untitled]; p. 34-37: I was the most beautiful blossom [Titled: Recitative Diana]; p. 38: Posterity is just around the corner; p. 39: Who cares?; p. 40: Come, come to Jesus / Dawn of a new day [untitled]; [Unidentified fragment]; p. 41-42: [Unidentified fragments]; p. 43: [Unidentified fragment]; Union Square; p. 44-50: [Unidentified fragments] (Box-folder 58/6)
    - Girl crazy sketches, GG holograph manuscript; [4] p.; p. 1: But not for me; Spanish; p. 2: [Unidentified fragment]; I got rhythm; p. 3: Summer, Winter, Spring, and Fall; Hot; p. 4: Tune; Tune (Box-folder 58/7)
    - Harmony exercises
      - GG holograph manuscript; [2] p. (Box-folder 58/8)